A Guide to the Blackley Family Papers, 1830-2016: SC 0232
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
- Series 4: Photographs, ca.1861-1989
  - Virginia Association of Broadcasters, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - WTON, 1951, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Stuart Hall, May Day, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Stuart Hall May Day, 1954 Cine-Kodak, Kodachrome Safety Color Film for 8mm roll cameras, 1954 (Box Freezer Storage)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Assorted Patricia Fry Blackley, 1963-1987, undated (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Catherine Matthews Blackley High School Reunion, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Chuck and Pat Blackley Wedding, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - National Association of Broadcasters, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Chas and Catherine Blackley 40th Anniversary Party, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Leckie Smokeless Coal Company Aerial Photographs, 1980-1981 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Contact Prints for Patton, Harris, Rust, & Associates, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Assorted Francis Matthews Stewart, 1987, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Chas and Catherine Blackley 50th Anniversary Party, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Chas Blackley's 80th Birthday Party, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Assorted Albert Lemain Phillips, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Assorted Negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Blackley Feed Store, undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Catherine Matthews Negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Chas Blackley Negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Chas and Mary Blackley, undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Dr. Chas C. Phillips, undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - John Matthews, undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - John Sewell Matthews, undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Lillie Bennett Matthews, undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Margaret Ester Dodson Matthews, undated (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Mrs. C.C. Phillips, undated (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Rev. Richard H. Phillips, undated (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Robert and Mary Blackley Taylor Wedding, undated (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Sallie Scott, undated (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Slides of the Blackley Family, undated (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Susie Phillips, undated (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - WSVA Office, undated (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Series 5: Scrapbooks, 1862-1931
  Series 5: Scrapbooks, 1862-1931, is comprised of four scrapbooks. In the aftermath of his wounding and the conclusion of the American Civil War, R. H. Bassett found a calling to participate in local and state politics. The majority of the first scrapbook contains newspaper clippings of news relating to his exploits and proclamations.
  The CMTC and VMI scrapbook highlights Chas Blackley's time with both of these organizations and places. The CMTC material is rare as the military's official website for the history of Ft. Eustis fails to even mention the fort's role during in that capacity.
  Finally, there are two scrapbooks document the journey that Chas Blackley and childhood friend, George Earman, made upon the steamer SS Gertrude Kellogg in 1930. Both scrapbooks chronicle Blackley and Earman's travels through the Pacific and multiple Asian nations.
  - R.H. Bassett Scrapbook, 1862-1869 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Chas Blackley, CMTC and VMI Scrapbook, 1928-1931 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Chas Blackley, S/S Gertrude Kellogg Scrapbook, 1930 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - S/S Gertrude Kellogg Scrapbook, 1930 (Box 26, Folder 4)